My name is Mary Alice Young.
我叫Mary Alice Young。
In this morning's paper, you may come across an article
在今天早上的论文中，您可能会遇到一篇文章
about the unusual day I had last week.
关于我上周经历的不寻常的一天
Normally, there's never anything newsworthy about my life,
通常，关于我的生活，没有任何新闻值得报道，
but that all changed last Thursday.
但这一切都在上周四发生了变化。
Of course, everything seemed quite normal at first.
当然，起初一切似乎都很正常。
I made breakfast for my family.
我为家人做早餐。
I performed my chores.
我做了家务。
I completed my projects.
我完成了我的项目。
I ran my errands.
我跑腿了。
In truth, I spent the day as I spent every other day,
说实话，我每天都过着一天，
quietly polishing the routine of my life until it gleamed with perfection.
悄悄地磨光我的生活，直到完美地闪闪发光。
That's why it was so astonishing when I decided to go to my hallway closet
这就是为什么当我决定去我的走廊壁橱时是如此令人惊讶的原因
and retrieve a revolver that had never been used.
并取回从未使用过的左轮手枪。
My body was discovered by my neighbor, Mrs. Martha Huber,
我的尸体是由邻居玛莎·胡伯夫人发现的，